nsnbc.me 2017-09-05

# nsnbc privacy policy - nsnbc international | nsnbc international

Any information which you provide directly to nsnbc ìnternational, such as your e-mail address when you comment or subscribe, is kept strictly private and is by no means passed on to a third party, for any reason, or under any circumstance.

Because our partner company, which is providing advertising on nsnbc ìnternational also adheres to a strict privacy policy, it is required, and we find it ethically correct and fair, that we give you the possibility to read the privacy policy in terms of our advertising on nsnbc.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Thank you for taking the time to informing yourself.

Christof Lehmann

Editor in Chief and Founder of nsnbc ìnternational
